Right girl. Wrong world.
Long Distance is a science fiction, comedy, action film directed by Will Speck.
After crash-landing on an alien planet, an asteroid miner must contend with the challenges of his new surroundings, while
making his way across the harsh terrain to the only other survivor – a woman who is trapped in her escape pod.
Andy Ramirez, played by Anthony Ramos.
Naomi Calloway, played by Naomi Scott.
Dwayne, played by Kristofer Hivju.
L.E.O.N.A.R.D. (voice), played by Zachary Quinto.
Mia Ramirez, played by Izzy Jones.
Caleb Ramirez, played by Leon Nurse-Joseph.
Long Distance is a 2024 American science fiction adventure film directed by
Josh Gordon and Will Speck, and written by Spenser Cohen.
The film stars Anthony Ramos, Naomi Scott, Kristofer Hivju, and Zachary Quinto.
Filming took place between September and November 2020.
Originally scheduled to be released theatrically as Distant on March 11, 2022, by Universal Pictures, Long
Distance was delayed several times before it was theatrically released in Vietnam on July 12, 2024.
It was released on Hulu in the United States on July 3, 2025, and removed
from the service at some point later in the same year.
The film explores themes of galaxy, alien, space, planet, spaceship.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.